<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
  <row>
    <Symbol Name>XAUUSD</Symbol Name>
    <Symbol Description>Gold/US Dollar</Symbol Description>
    <Contract Size>100</Contract Size>
    <Digit>2</Digit>
    <Leverage>1:100</Leverage>
    <_1 Pip PL>10</_1 Pip PL>
    <Quote CCY>USD</Quote CCY>
    <FIELD8>XAUUSD is a currency pair that represents the exchange rate between gold (XAU) and the US dollar. It shows how many US dollars are required to buy one troy ounce of gold.
 
 Gold is a popular asset for investors and traders around the world, and XAUUSD is actively traded in the global financial markets.
 
 The average daily trading volume of XAUUSD is approximately $183 billion.</FIELD8>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Symbol Name>XAGUSD</Symbol Name>
    <Symbol Description>Silver/US Dollar</Symbol Description>
    <Contract Size>5000</Contract Size>
    <Digit>3</Digit>
    <Leverage>1:100</Leverage>
    <_1 Pip PL>5</_1 Pip PL>
    <Quote CCY>USD</Quote CCY>
    <FIELD8>XAGUSD is a currency pair that represents the exchange rate between silver (XAG) and the US dollar. It shows how many US dollars are required to buy one troy ounce of silver.
 
 Silver is a popular asset for investors and traders around the world, and XAGUSD is actively traded in the global financial markets.
 
 The average daily trading volume of XAGUSD is approximately $15.6 billion.
 
 XAGUSD is not considered a traditional currency pair, but it is still actively traded in the forex market.</FIELD8>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Symbol Name>XAUEUR</Symbol Name>
    <Symbol Description>Gold/Euro</Symbol Description>
    <Contract Size>100</Contract Size>
    <Digit>2</Digit>
    <Leverage>1:100</Leverage>
    <_1 Pip PL>10</_1 Pip PL>
    <Quote CCY>EUR</Quote CCY>
    <FIELD8>XAUEUR is a currency pair that represents the exchange rate between gold (XAU) and the euro. It shows how many euros are required to buy one troy ounce of gold.
 
 Gold is a popular asset for investors and traders around the world, and XAUEUR is actively traded in the global financial markets. The pair is often influenced by a variety of factors, including economic data releases, geopolitical events, global market sentiment, and inflation expectations.
 
 The average daily trading volume of XAUEUR is approximately $183 billion.</FIELD8>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Symbol Name>XPDUSD</Symbol Name>
    <Symbol Description>Palladium/US Dollar</Symbol Description>
    <Contract Size>100</Contract Size>
    <Digit>2</Digit>
    <Leverage>1:100</Leverage>
    <_1 Pip PL>10</_1 Pip PL>
    <Quote CCY>USD</Quote CCY>
    <FIELD8>XPDUSD is a currency pair that represents the exchange rate between palladium (XPD) and the US dollar. It shows how many US dollars are required to buy one troy ounce of palladium.
 
 Palladium is a rare and valuable precious metal that is used in a variety of industrial applications, including catalytic converters for vehicles. XPDUSD is actively traded in the global financial markets, and the pair is often influenced by a variety of factors, including economic data releases, geopolitical events, global market sentiment, and demand for palladium in industrial applications.</FIELD8>
  </row>
  <row>
    <Symbol Name>XPTUSD</Symbol Name>
    <Symbol Description>Palladium/US Dollar</Symbol Description>
    <Contract Size>50</Contract Size>
    <Digit>2</Digit>
    <Leverage>1:50</Leverage>
    <_1 Pip PL>5</_1 Pip PL>
    <Quote CCY>USD</Quote CCY>
    <FIELD8>XPTUSD is a currency pair that represents the exchange rate between platinum (XPT) and the US dollar. It shows how many US dollars are required to buy one troy ounce of platinum.
 
 Platinum is a rare and valuable precious metal that is used in a variety of industrial applications, including catalytic converters for vehicles and jewelry. XPTUSD is actively traded in the global financial markets, and the pair is often influenced by a variety of factors, including economic data releases, geopolitical events, global market sentiment, and demand for platinum in industrial and consumer applications.</FIELD8>
  </row>
</root>
